(Sheldon:)I don't care. There are far too many
historical anomalies for my comfort.
Oh, okay, how about this?
(Raj:)You can go dressed
as a Star Trek science officer...
(Raj:)...exploring a planet similar to Earth
in the 1500s.
(Sheldon:)You mean like Spock?
(Leonard:)Sure.
(Sheldon:)Fascinating.
- Hey, fellow scientists. Sheldon.
LEONARD: Mm.
Why don't we move there
so Leslie can join us?
Yeah, let's do it.
(Sheldon:)If you're having trouble
deciding where to sit...
(Sheldon:)...I suggest One Potato, Two Potato...
(Sheldon:)...or as I call it, the Leslie Winkle
Experimental Methodology.
- Don't make this hard for me.
- It's not hard. It's simple.
(Sheldon:)You can either sit with me,
your friend, colleague and roommate...
(Sheldon:)...or you can sit with an overrated scientist
you might have sex with.